[{"answer": "Yes, since the last time I saw you, I thought you would never invite me back.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "Yes, it's a Chateau le Tour.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Chateau le Tour?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "They are not.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Are they called the Fallonettes?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Thanks, god.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "How do you jump this rock star shot?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "The new look -- I'm just losing --", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "The new look?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "I just have this compilation of all this music and maybe it is going in my ahead a little bit.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Are you not taken so seriously as a rock star?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "\"Whip My Hair.\"", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Bruce Springsteen, I mean incredibly, you got him to cover Willis Smith's hit, right?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "The Boss.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "-- The Boss?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Is he serious?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Listen, it's a brilliant album.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "And it's like, if you think about it, when would he -- when would he ever see Bruce dressed like he was 30 years ago?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "It was one of these weird things.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "How did you persuade him to do that?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Or did you deliberately lose to her to try and get the --", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "It's just the joy of competition, you know?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "No, because we did everything inside the White House.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "-- with the president?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, the goal of this is to get children to get fit and workout and do --", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think you're enhancing the reputation of your nation and its great leader by doing a sack race the East Room, a potato race?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "And you had a private meeting with the president before this -- the slow jam?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, the -- it's -- by protocol, they want you to meet the president alone, because you invited him, so you -- so I'm -- I have to be there in -- no -- no stage manager, no assistants, no Fallonettes, no one is allowed to --", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "How does that go?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "-- why would I impersonate someone with three minutes left --", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "-- who would it be?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Don't be so American literal about this.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "I want to show God my act?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "So this \"Call Me Maybe,\" even my kids back in England, who wouldn't necessarily know who you are, now know you're the guy from the \"Call Me Maybe\" clip, because two million hits on YouTube.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Can you get more index cards laid out?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't turn it down.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Would you turn down the \"Tonight Show\" if you were offered it?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Is it -- is it the Holy Grail?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "ALLON: I don't think so.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I think it's the story around it, but it's not.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Hasn't it always been the Holy Grail as a -- as a talk show host in America?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "It's -- they Google.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What is the kind of interview that absolutely sends you demented?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "You're starting right off there.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "What do you think of America right now?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "That's a really good question.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "How much has that guided your sense of people not being reliant on their parents?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Are you an Obama man at heart?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Moral compass.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What is the kind of leader that you're craving in an American president?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "More than one and less than five.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Do you want to name how many you've rolled in the hay with?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "She actually has a hay bale in her bedroom.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Did you actually roll in the hay with her?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I have no problem with that.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Why shouldn't their opinion, their Tweets be as valuable to the world as yours or mine?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "What's interesting about it in my life is I made some great albums in the '90s and -- which become sort of almost like a mill stone around my neck.", "docId": "120623pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "What do you feel about this album?", "qSentId": 646}]